Guide to the Stanford Historical Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford historical photograph collection
circa 1887-circa 1996
SC1071
Stanford University. Libraries. Department of Special Collections and University Archives.
43 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The collection is open for research.
Alternative Formats
The Stanford Historical Photograph Collection is available online as one of Stanford's Insight image databases. You may access the images here: http://insight.stanford.edu/luna/servlet/Stanford~4~1.
Associated Materials
More recent photographs can be found at the Stanford News Service.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
The Stanford Photograph Collection contains over 16,000 images of Stanford scenes including photographs of and relating to the Stanford family, views of the campus and individual buildings, photographs of students and student life activities, and photographs of faculty and administrative staff. The majority of photographs are black and white gelatin prints but nineteenth-century albumen prints mounted on boards are also represented. The collection spans the late 1890s through the 1990s.
Access Terms
Central Pacific Railroad Company; Palo Alto Stock Farm (Stanford, Calif.); Stanford University -- General subdivision--Sports.;; Photoprints.; San Francisco Earthquake and Fire, Calif., 1906; Stanford University--Athletics; Stanford University--Buildings.; Stanford University--Faculty.; Stanford University--History.; Stanford University--Students.
Collection Contents
- General Photographs, Series 1
  General photographs pertaining to Stanford University arranged by subjects (i.e., "athletics," "campus scenes," "student life," and the like).
  - Administration Building--Outer Quad (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adobe Hut [Buelna?] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American Conference (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Groups--Fol. 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Groups--Fol. 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni--Half Century Club (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Studies, Seminars in (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Pioneer Trails Assoc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Angel of Grief--Pre-Earthquake (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Angel of Grief--Post-Earthquake (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Applied Electronics Laboratory (AEL) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arboretum--Fol.1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arboretum--Fol.2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Architecture, Program in (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Army Specialized Training Program--Fol.1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Army Specialized Training Program--Fol.2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Army Specialized Training Program--Fol.3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Art Department--Fol.1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Art Department--Fol.2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Art Gallery--Fol.1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Art Gallery--Fol.2 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assembly Hall (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Athletic Facilities (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Facilities--Angell Field (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Facilities--Basketball Pavilion (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Facilities--Encina Gym I (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Facilities--Encina Gym II and Pools (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Facilities--Golf Course (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Facilities--Maples Pavilion (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Facilities--Roble Gym I (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Facilities--Roble Gym II (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Facilities--Stadium--Fol.1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Facilities--Stadium--Fol.2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Facilities--Stadium Pre-1921 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Facilities--Tennis Stadium (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Athletics--Baseball--Action Shots (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Baseball--Individual Players (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Baseball--Team Pictures--Fol.1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Baseball--Team Pictures--Fol.2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Athletics--Basketball--Action Shots (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Athletics--Basketball--Individuals (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Athletics--Basketball--Team Pictures (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Athletics--Boxing (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Athletics--Coaches and Captains (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Athletics--Coaches--Maloney, Harry W. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Athletics--Crew--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Athletics--Crew--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Athletics--Fencing (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Football--Action Shots--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Athletics--Football--Action Shots--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Athletics--Football--Action Shots--Fol.3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Athletics--Football--Action Shots--Fol.4 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Athletics--Football--Action Shots--Fol.5 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Football--Big Game--Action Shots--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Football--Big Game--Action Shots--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Athletics--Football--Big Game--Action Shots--Fol.3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Athletics--Football--Big Game--Action Shots--Rugby--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Athletics--Football--Big Game--Action Shots--Rugby--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Athletics--Football--Coaches--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Football--Coaches--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Football--Coaches--Glenn S. Warner--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Football--Coaches--Glenn S. Warner--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Fol.6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Athletics--Football--Individual Players--Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Athletics--Football--Misc. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Football--Practices--Fol.1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.1, 1971-- (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.2, 1971-- (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.3, 1971-- (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.4, 1971-- (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.5, 1971-- (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.1, 1972-- (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.2, 1972-- (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.3, 1972-- (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.4, 1972-- (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Athletics--Football--Rose Bowl-- Fol.5, 1972-- (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rose Bowl (panorama), 2013 Jan 1
  - Athletics--Football--Team Pictures--Fol.1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Football--Team Pictures--Fol.2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Athletics--Football--Team Pictures--Fol.3 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Athletics--Football--Team Pictures--Fol.4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Athletics--Football--Team Pictures--Fol.5 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Athletics--Football--Tournament of Roses, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Football--Tournament of Roses--Floats (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Golf (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Athletics--Gymnastics (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Athletics--Intramural (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Athletics--Karate (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Polo (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Rugby (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Service Projects (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Athletics--Soccer (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Athletics--Swimming--Fol.1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Athletics--Swimming--Fol.2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Athletics--Tennis--Fol.1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.6 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.7 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Track--Action Shots--Fol.8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Track--Coaches (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Athletics--Track--Individuals--Fol.1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Athletics--Track--Individuals--Fol.2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Athletics--Track--Individuals--Fol.3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Athletics--Track--Individuals--Fol.4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Track--Olympic Tryouts, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Track--Team Pictures--Fol.1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Track--Team Pictures--Fol.2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Athletics--Track--Team Pictures--Fol.3 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Athletics--Trainers (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Athletics--Water Polo (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Action Shots--Fol.1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Action Shots--Fol.2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Individuals--Fol.1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Individuals--Fol.2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Team Pictures--Fol.1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Women's Basketball--Team Pictures--Fol.2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Athletics--Women's Dance (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Athletics--Women's Exercises (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Athletics--Women's Fencing (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Athletics--Women's Field Hockey (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Women's Football (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Women's Gymnastics--Fol.1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Athletics--Women's Gymnastics--Fol.2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Athletics--Women's Gymnastics--Fol.3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Athletics--Women's Gymnastics--Mosher/Martin Tests (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Athletics--Women's Miscellaneous Sports (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Athletics--Women's Physical Education Staff (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Athletics--Women's Tennis (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Athletics--Wrestling (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Axe--Stanford (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Band, Stanford--Fol.1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Band, Stanford--Fol.2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Band, Stanford--Fol.3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Band, Stanford--Big Game (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bandstand (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bench and Bar (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1920's (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Beta Theta Pi, c.1924 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1927-1928 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Beta Theta Pi-- Fol.1, 1930's-- (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Beta Theta Pi-- Fol.2, 1930's-- (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Beta Theta Pi-- Caricatures, 1930's-- (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Beta Theta Pi-- Fol.1, 1940's-- (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Beta Theta Pi-- Fol.2, 1940's-- (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1950's (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Bicycle shop (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Big Game Activities (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Big Game Activities--Bonfire--Fol.1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Big Game Activities--Bonfire--Fol.2 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Biological Sciences--Faculty (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Black Student Union (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Block "S" Society (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Bookstore--Exterior (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bookstore--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bookstore--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bookstore--Interior--Fol.3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bookstore--Interior--Fol.4 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bookstore--Pre-1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bookstore--Proof Sheets (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Branner, John Casper--Residence (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cactus Garden--Fol.1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cactus Garden--Fol.2 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cactus Garden--Fol.3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Camp, The (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Camp Fremont (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Campus--Aerial Views--Fol.1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Campus--Aerial Views--Fol.2 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Campus--Aerial Views--Fol.3 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Campus--Aerial Views--Fol.4 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Campus--Farming (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Campus Lands (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Campus Lands--Fol.2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.4 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.6 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Campus Lands--Aerial Survey--Fol.7 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Campus Planning--Fol.1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Campus Planning--Fol.2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Campus Planning--Olmsted/Coolidge--Fol.1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Campus Planning--Olmsted/Coolidge--Fol.2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Campus Planning--Olmsted/Coolidge--Fol.3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Campus Roads--Fol.1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Campus Roads--Fol.2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Campus Roads--Fol.3 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Campus Scenes--Pre-1906 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Campus Scenes--Pre-1906--Across Lake Lagunita--Fol. 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Campus Scenes--Pre-1906--Across Lake Lagunita--Fol. 2 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Campus Scenes--Pre-1906--Across Lake Lagunita--Fol. 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Campus Scenes--Pre-1906--Across Lake Lagunita--Fol. 4 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Campus Scenes--Post 1906 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Campus Scenes--Post 1906--Across Lake Lagunita (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Campus--Views from Hoover Tower (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Candy Store (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Carillon (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, D.C. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Carnot Medal (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cedro Cottage--Fol.1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cedro Cottage--Fol.2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cellar, The (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Chaparral, The (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Chapel--First at Stanford (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry Building--Exterior--Pre-1906--Fol.1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry Building--Exterior--Pre-1906--Fol.2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Chemistry Building--Exterior--Post-1906--Fol.1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Chemistry Building--Exterior--Post-1906--Fol.2 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Chemistry Building--Interior (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry Department--Faculty--Fol.1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry Department--Faculty--Fol.2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Chess Club (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Civil Affairs Training School (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Civilian Defense School (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Class Hats (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1895 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1895--The `95 Oak (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1896 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1898 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1899 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1903 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1924 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1926 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1929 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1930 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1940 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Class Plates (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Clock Tower--New (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Clock Tower--Old (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - College Terrace (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Commencement (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Commencement, 1899 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Commencement, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Commencement, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Commencement, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Commencement, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Commencement, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Commencement, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Commencement, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Commencement, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Commencement, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Commencement, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Commencement, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Commencement, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Commencement, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Commencement, c.1940 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Commencement-- Fol.1, 1941-- (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Commencement-- Fol.2, 1941-- (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Commencement, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Communication, Department of (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Construction--Athletic Facilities (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Construction--Bookstore--Fol.1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Construction--Bookstore--Fol.2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Construction--Bookstore--Fol.3 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Construction--Branner Hall (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Construction--Braun Music Center (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Construction--Business School (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Construction--Business School--Outer Quad (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Construction--Chemistry Building (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Construction--Crothers and Crothers Memorial Halls (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Construction--Cummings Art Building (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Construction--Education Building (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Construction--Encina Commons (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Construction--Encina Hall (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Construction--Encina Hall--Renovation (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Construction--Engineering Laboratories (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Construction--Gymnasium--Men--1906 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Construction--High Energy Physics Laboratory (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Construction--Hoover, Lou Henry House (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Construction--Hoover Tower (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Construction--Knoll, The (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Construction--Lake Lagunita--Boathouse (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Construction--Law School--Outer Quad (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Construction--Library (1906) (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Construction--Library (1919) (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Construction--Mausoleum (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Construction--Medical Center (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Construction--Memorial Arch--Fol.1 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Construction--Memorial Arch--Fol.2 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Construction--Memorial Arch--Fol.3 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Construction--Memorial Church--Fol.1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Construction--Memorial Church--Fol.2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Construction--Memorial Court (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Construction--Memorial Hall--Fol.1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Construction--Memorial Hall--Fol.2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Construction--Meyer Library (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Construction--Mitchell Earth Sciences Building (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Construction--Museum--Fol.1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Construction--Museum--Fol.2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Construction--Physics Lecture Hall (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Construction--Post Office (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Construction--Power House (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.5 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.6 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.7 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.8 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Construction--Quad--Fol.9 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Construction--Quad--Goodrich Quarry (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Construction--Quad--Locomotive Used (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Construction--Quad--Renovation (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Construction--Quad--Renovation--Mathematics Corner--Fol.1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Construction--Quad--Renovation--Mathematics Corner--Fol.2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Construction--Roble Hall II (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Construction--Ryan High Voltage Laboratory (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Construction--Sequoia Hall--(1951)--Fol.1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Construction--Sequoia Hall--(1951)--Fol.2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Construction--Stadium--Fol.1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Construction--Stadium--Fol.2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Construction--Stadium--Fol.3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Construction--Stauffer Chemistry Buildings (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Construction--Stern Hall (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Construction--Toyon Hall (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Construction--Wilbur Hall (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Construction--Workers--Fol.1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Construction--Workers--Fol.2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cooksey House (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cornerstone--Fol.1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Cornerstone--Fol.2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Corporation Yard (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Coutts, Peter--Buildings (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Coutts, Peter--Buildings--Dog House (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Coutts, Peter--Buildings--Escondite Cottage--Fol.1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Coutts, Peter--Buildings--Escondite Cottage--Fol.2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Coutts, Peter--Frenchman's Bridge (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Coutts, Peter--Frenchman's Tower (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Coutts, Peter--Lands (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Coutts, Peter--Water Projects--Fol.1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Coutts, Peter--Water Projects--Fol.2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Daily Palo Alto (renamed The Stanford Daily in 1926) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Dinkelspiel Auditorium (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Dohrmann Memorial Grove (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Douglas Chair (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Drama, Student (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Drama, Student--Wendell Cole Collection--Fol.1 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Drama, Student--Wendell Cole Collection--Fol.2 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Dudley Herbarium (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Agassiz Statue--Fol.1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Agassiz Statue--Fol.2 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Angel of Grief (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Chemistry Building (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Encina Hall (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Engineering Laboratories (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Entrance Gate (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Faculty Committee (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Gymnasium--Men--(1906)--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Gymnasium--Men--(1906)--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Library--(1906)--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Library--(1906)--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Library--(1906)--Fol.3 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Arch--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Arch--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Arch--Fol.3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Exterior--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Exterior--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Exterior--Fol.3 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Memorial Church--Reconstruction (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Museum--Exterior--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Museum--Exterior--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Museum--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Museum--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Palo Alto (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Power House and Chimney (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Quad--Fol.1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Quad--Fol.2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Redwood City (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Earthquake (1906)--San Andreas Fault (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Earthquake (1906)--San Francisco (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Earthquake (1906)--S.B. Dole Collection (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Student Residences--Fol.1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Earthquake (1906)--Student Residences--Fol.2 (Box 19, Folder 10)